KAH YEE CHIANG

Kuala Lumpur | kahyee.chiang@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/kahyeechiang | kahyee.com

SUMMARY

Product manager bringing global experience from living in 7 countries and working on consumer and enterprise products at various startups and multinationals. My experience building my new university as part of the inaugural class has instilled my passion for building user-centric products and technologies.

EXPERIENCE

Jirnexu • Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

July 2020 - Present

Product Manager

Working on RinggitPlus.com to simplify finances for Malaysians

Scoop Technologies • San Francisco, CA

Aug 2019 - April 2020

Associate Product Manager

- Led on-time development of the first enterprise feature to be rolled out to all of Scoop's Fortune 100 customers which would unlock moving customers from a trip-based pricing model to a platform-based SaaS pricing model by visualizing ROI
- Spearheaded a complex architectural addition to the underlying technical definitions of customers, which required backend, frontend, data/ETL work
- Conducted user research, journey mapping, and user acquisition funnel analysis of enterprise buyers
- Managed and prioritized 40+ accessibility bugs; implemented 80+ XML copy changes across iOS and Android
- Build and deployed a no-code app to ~700 users across multiple markets and geographies by collaborating with product marketing for copy, visuals, user segmentation and targeting
- Conducted technical research to evaluate capabilities of third party integrations to unblock the launch of ~40k
 new potential users at 3 new markets

Rockerbox • Remote Oct 2018 - April 2019

Product Growth Associate

Managed leads pipeline in Salesforce & owned paid search marketing campaigns on AdWords

Maker Media • San Francisco, CA

May 2018 - Aug 2019

Product Management Intern

- Conducted research to suggest a new product vision and roadmap to CEO for a digital learning product
- Analyzed NPS score data to provide recommendations, using multivariate regressions, decision trees, and pivot tables in R

Cox Communications • Remote

Oct 2017 - April 2018

Product Development Consultant

Created and tested 3 prototypes for a new product line, reported to the VP of Strategic Planning & Analysis

EDUCATION

Minerva Schools at KGI • Summa Cum Laude, GPA: 3.8/4.0

2015 - 2019

BSc in Business: Brand Management, Managing Operational Complexity, Scalable Growth